{"data":[{"question":"Have you ______ football today?","a":"played","b":"playied","c":"plaid","d":"playd","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Play- Played - Played","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He ___ a loaf of bread.","a":"buy","b":"buyed","c":"bought","d":"buyd","answer":"3","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Buy - Bought - Bought","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They haven't ______ the film yet.","a":"see","b":"saw","c":"seen","d":"seeing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- See - Saw - Seen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We ______ to her yesterday.","a":"speak","b":"spoke","c":"spoken","d":"speaked","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Speak - spoke - spoken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They ______ in London for two years.","a":"live","b":"lived","c":"living","d":"are living","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Live - Lived - Lived","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The children haven't arrived ______ home yet.","a":"in","b":"-","c":"at","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We say \" arrive home\" without any preposition","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Haven't they ______ you the books yet?","a":"given","b":"gave","c":"giving","d":"give","answer":"1","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Give - Gave - Given","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you seen him? No, he hasn't arrived _______ home yet.","a":"-","b":"in","c":"on","d":"at","answer":"1","explain":"- We say \" arrive home\" without any prepositions","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He ______ to buy the newspaper.","a":"stop","b":"stopped","c":"stoped","d":"stoppen","answer":"2","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Stop - Stopped - Stopped","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She has already arrived ______ home.","a":"on","b":"in","c":"at","d":"-","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We say \" arrive home\" without any preposition","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}